(Sheldon:)...from Victorian England
into the post-apocalyptic future...
...where society had splintered
into two factions:
(Sheldon:)the subterranean Morlocks...
(Sheldon:)...who survived by feasting on the flesh
of the gentle surface-dwelling Eloi.
(Howard:)Talk about your chick magnets.
(Raj:)Oh, yeah. The guy who lives next to me
is always like:
"I have a Jacuzzi on my balcony.
I have a Jacuzzi on my balcony."
(Raj:)But wait until I tell him
I've got a time machine on my balcony.
(Raj:)Stuff that in your Speedos, Jacuzzi Bob.
Gentlemen, we said we'd take turns...
...but I think you'll agree
that practicality dictates it remain here.
You can't keep it.
What if I meet a girl and say:
"You wanna see my time machine?
It's at my friend's house."
(Howard:)How lame is that?
- He's got a point.
SHELDON: All right.
(Sheldon:)We're going to need some ground rules.
"No shoes in the time machine."
"No eating in the time machine."
I propose that we add:
"Pants must be worn at all times
in the time machine."